<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Coding challenge</string>
    <string name="btnTextOne_mainActivity">Text one</string>
    <string name="btnTextTwo_mainActivity">Text two</string>
    <string name="btnTextThree_mainActivity">Text three</string>
    <string name="label_Manifest_SecondActivity">Your article</string>
    <string name="textOne_mainActivity_article">The Right Honourable Sir Winston Leonard Spencer-Churchill, KG. ОМ. CH. FRS (November 30, 1874 — January 24, 1965) was a British politician, best known as Prime Minister of the United Kingdom during World War II. At various times an author, soldier, journalist, legislator and painter, Churchill is generally regarded as one of the most important leaders in British and world history. \n
        Winston Churchill was born at Blenheim Palace, near Woodstock in Oxfordshire. Winston’s father, Lord Randolph Churchill, was a politician. Winston’s mother, Lady Randolph Churchill of Brooklyn, New York, was a daughter of American millionaire Leonard Jerome. As the son of a prominent politician, it was unsurprising that Churchill was soon drawn into politics himself. \n
        He started speaking at a number of Conservative meetings in the 1890s. In the 1906 general election, Churchill won a seat in Manchester. He served as Under Secretary of State for the Colonies. Churchill soon became the most prominent member of the Government. At the outbreak of the Second World War Churchill was appointed First Lord of the Admiralty. He was an early supporter of the pan-Europeanism that led to the formation of the European Common market and later the European Union (for which one of the three main buildings of the European Parliament is named in his honour). \n
        Miscellany — In 1953 he was awarded two major honours. He was knighted and became Sir Winston Churchill and he was awarded the Nobel Prize for Literature "for his mastery of historical and biographical description as well as for brilliant oratory in defending exalted human values. He was named Time Magazine "Man of the Halt-Century" in the early 1950s. In 1959 Churchill inherited the title of Father of the House. He became the MP with the longest continuous service — since 1924.
        Churchill College, a constituent college of the University of Cambridge, was founded in 1960 as the national and commonwealth memorial to Winston Churchill. Churchill was voted as "The Greatest Briton" in 2002 "100 Greatest Britons" poll sponsored by the BBC and voted for by the public.</string>
    <string name="textOneHeading_mainActivity_HeadingArticle">British famous people: Winston Churchill</string>
    <string name="textTwo_mainActivity_article">Christmas Day is one of the most favorite American holidays It is celebrated on December 25. Christmas is a Christian holiday marking the birth of the Christ Child. Decorating houses and yards with lights, putting up Christmas trees, giving gifts, and sending greeting cards have become traditions even for many non-Christian Americans "here also a tradition to place a decorated Christmas tree in the White House, the official home in Washington D.C. of the President of the USA.
        The tradition of placing a decorated tree in the White House began in 1889 on Christmas morning during the Presidency of Benjamin Harrison. The President’s grandchildren young Benjamin and Mary McKee, led the Harrison household into the second floor Oval Room to take a look at the first White House Christmas tree. It was lit with candles. Filled stockings hung from the mantel. Presents, candy and nuts were distributed to family and staff. President Harrison gave turkeys and gloves to his employees. He received a silver-dollar-shaped picture holder from his daughter, Mame Harrison McKee.
        What began as a family gathering has become a national tradition. Over the years, the White House Christmas tree has reflected both the times and the tastes of the First Family. First Lady Frances Cleveland created a "technology savvy" tree in 1895 when she hung electric lights on the White House tree. First Lady Jacqueline Kennedy began the tradition of Christmas Tree themes when she decorated the 1961 Christmas tree in toy trimmings from the Nutcracker Suite ballet by Tchaikovsky.
        Today, the First Lady selects a theme and taps the talents of American artisans, who give life to the idea. Laura Bush chose "Home for the Holidays" for the 2001 theme, which features replicas of the family homes of the nation’s Presidents. The Presidents Christmas tree can be viewed by anyone either in the news programs, or on the official web site of the White House.</string>
    <string name="textTwoHeading_mainActivity_HeadingArticle">Christmas</string>
    <string name="textThree_mainActivity_article">Over the centuries Ukrainian people have developed their own arts of music, theatre, and painting. Some Ukrainian artists and their masterpieces are famous not only in Ukraine but also all over the world.
        Ukrainian music has a long history. Folk traditions have preserved to this day original songs, lyrical, humorous, and patriotic and others. «Kobza», «bandura», «sopilka» are among most famous national musical instruments. «Kobza» is a unique musical instrument. The one who plays it is called «kobzar». One of the most famous kobzars was Hnat Honcharenko. Blind from childhood, he learned to play kobza at 20—22 and wandered singing and playing dumas, psalms, and humorous songs and teaching other kobzars. He spent the last part of his life mostly in Sevastopol. In 1908 Lesia Ukrainka took Honcharenko to Yalta and, with her husband K.Kvitka recorded his dumas. Speaking about Ukrainian composers, we must mention I. Stravinsky and S. Prokofiev, who were born in Ukraine. M. Lysenko, a pianist, composer, conductor and folklorist was an important figure of the Ukrainian musical renaissance. Among his operas there are the well-known «Taras Bulba» and «Natalka Poltavka».
        In Ukraine the oldest surviving paintings are frescoes found on the northern Black Sea coast. Famous frescoes of St. Sophia Cathedral in Kiev and of the Armenian Cathedral in Lvov are one of the oldest and attract many tourists from Ukraine and abroad. After the Academy of Arts in St. Petersburg was established, many talented painters moved to Russia. This emigration deprived Ukrainian painting of its most creative talents. But there were several exceptions that devoted most of their painting to Ukrainian interests. Among such painters was T. Shevchenko, who is considered the father of modern Ukrainian painting. One more famous representative of the Ukrainian art was Ilia Repin. He was an outstanding painter, full member of the St. Petersburg Academy of Arts. Many of his works show Ukraine, its people and its history. Among them there are the most famous painting "The Zhaporozhian Cossacks Write a Letter to the Turkish Sultan", "Evening Party", "Haidamakys", "Cossack in the Steppe", and "Hopak". He also painted many portraits of Russian and Ukrainian cultural figures. Among them were M. Kostomarov, I. Kramskoi, T. Shevchenko and others.
        The history of Ukrainian theatre also goes back to the ancient times. We may find their traces in pre-Christian traditions and rituals. They are evident even today in the summer Kupalo festival, the winter carols and above all in the ceremony of the Ukrainian wedding. The further development of Ukrainian theatre was influenced by European medieval theatre traditions. The first Ukrainian language plays of I. Kotliarevsky and H. Kvitka-Osnovianenko were staged by Poltava Free Theatre in 1819. Many Ukrainian landlords organized serf theatres at their estates. In their theatres Ukrainian plays were performed. In Russian-ruled Ukraine many amateur and touring theatre groups were active. The leaders in organizing them were M. Starytsky and I. Karpenko-Kary. The first professional Ukrainian theatre was a touring troupe in Austrian-ruled Galicia and Bukovina. It was directed by O. Bachynsky. The times of the Soviet rule were not easy for Ukrainian theatre. Over the past few years the Ukrainian theatre is on the wave of national revival. Many youth theatres, musical comedies and theatre stars have appeared.</string>
    <string name="textThreeHeading_mainActivity_HeadingArticle">Art in Ukraine</string>
    <string name="logD_mainActivity_ButtonOneClicked">Button one clicked!</string>
    <string name="logD_mainActivity_ButtonTwoClicked">Button two clicked!</string>
    <string name="logD_mainActivity_ButtonThreeClicked">Button three clicked!</string>
</resources>
