<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CodelabsAndroidCourse</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_firstRecipeTitle">Kale Lemon Sandwiches</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_firstRecipeDescription">This sandwich is stunningly delicious and tastes as good as it is healthy. Any greens of choice will work. The lemon adds an almost sweet taste. Be generous with it!</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_secondRecipeDescription">Everyone loves this, so double or even triple the recipe! It vanishes in a flash, and also works well as a salsa. It really is our all-time favorite summer salad. The red onion adds a dash of color and the zest (the peel) intensifies the lime flavor.</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_secondRecipeTitle">Mango-lime bean salad</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_thirdRecipeTitle">Sweet Potato and Lentil Soup with Shiitake Mushrooms</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_thirdRecipeDescription">This soup is so good Essy and I ate it ALL the first time I made it. If someone is hesitant about plant-based food, this has to be a convincer. Red lentils keep this soup a beautiful orange color. If you don’t have leeks use onions. Serve it alone or over rice with a big green salad.</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_fourthRecipeTitle">Lime mousse</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_fourthRecipeDescription">This is FABULOUS alone, topped with fruit of any kind or as a frosting on cake. It is fast to make at the last minute. Use more or less lime according to taste.</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_fifthRecipeDescription">Flavorful recipe for this farm raised fish that is easy and done in minutes! The fish is broiled with a creamy cheese coating for an impressive flavor and texture.</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_fifthRecipeTitle">Broiled Tilapia Parmesan</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_firstRecipeIngredients">
        4 slices Mestemacher of Feldcamp (Whole Foods) or any whole grain bread – I’ve used squaw bread from Sprouts or Ezekiel sprouted bread
        1 bunch of kale, chopped in bite sized pieces (remove thick stem) or Swiss Chard or greens of choice (4 cups or more) – I use kale (Lacinato)
        hummus without tahini (easy to make blending  a base of chick peas, lemon and garlic then adding to taste cumin, vinegar, red peppers, parsley or cilantro
        Green onions chopped  (1 per slice of bread) – Red onion is good too!!
        1/2 to 1 bunch cilantro or parsley, chopped – I use cilantro
        1/2- 1 lemon, center part VERY, VERY thinly sliced and the ends squeezed and zested – I love lemon so I use extra
        1 large tomato, sliced in 4 thick slices (optional)
        Broccoli sprouts (optional but good!)
        Black pepper, to taste</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_secondRecipeIngredients">
        1 mango, peeled and diced
        One 15-oz can cannellini beans, drained and rinsed.
        [one cup, a little less, also works; amount is not critical]
        Red onion, diced, to taste (about a half an onion
        Cilantro . . a lot  (1/2 cup or more!)
        Zest of 1 lime  Juice of 1 juicy lime, squeezed.</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_thirdRecipeIngredients">
        1 leak ; thinly sliced
        6 cloves garlic ; minced
        2 cups shitake musrooms ; soaked for 30 min before sliceing
        4 cups vegetable broth
        2 cups water
        1 1/2 cups lentils
        1 sweet potato ; diced
        1 bay leaf
        1/2 cup basil
        dash Black pepper
        handful spinach</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_fourthRecipeIngredients">
        1 cup heavy whipping cream.
        1/4 cup sugar.
        2 tablespoons lime juice.
        1 tablespoon grated lime zest.
        1 teaspoon vanilla extract.
        Lime slices and fresh mint, optional.</string>
    <string name="tv_mainActivity_fifthRecipeIngredients">
        1/2 cup Parmesan cheese
        1/4 cup butter, softened
        3 tablespoons mayonnaise
        2 tablespoons fresh lemon juice
        1/4 teaspoon dried basil
        1/4 teaspoon ground black pepper
        1/8 teaspoon onion powder
        1/8 teaspoon celery salt
        2 pounds tilapia fillets</string>
</resources>
